<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>On-site Sewage Disposal Systems - Oahu</title>
                <onlink>https://geodata.hawaii.gov/arcgis/rest/services/Infrastructure/MapServer/22</onlink>
                <onlink>https://files.hawaii.gov/dbedt/op/gis/data/osds_oah.pdf</onlink>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>[Metadata] On-site sewage disposal systems (osds) for the 
island of Oahu as of 2008.  Approximate location, type, effluent, 
nitrogen and phosphorus flux of on-site sewage disposal systems.Source:  State of Hawaii Department of Health, May, 2017.Developed in 2008 as part of the Hawaii 
State Department of Health source water protection program to assess the
 health and environmental risks posed by on-site sewage disposal 
systems.For additional information, please refer to complete metadata at https://files.hawaii.gov/dbedt/op/gis/data/osds_oah.pdf or contact Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, Office of Planning and Sustainable Development, State of Hawaii; PO Box 2359, Honolulu, Hi. 96804; (808) 587-2846; email: gis@hawaii.gov; Website: https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis.</abstract>
            <purpose>On-site Sewage Disposal Systems for the island of Oahu, as of 2008.</purpose>
        </descript>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>Infrastructure</themekey>
                <themekey>Sewage</themekey>
                <themekey>Water Quality</themekey>
                <themekey>Cesspools</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>State of Hawaii Terms of Use. 



The
 contents of this web page are public domain and to the extent indicated
 otherwise in the Terms of Use, are exempt from Terms of Use policy 
restrictions.There are no expressed warranties associated with the 
release of this data or product. Specifically, no warranty is made that 
the GIS data or any subsequent updates will be error free and no 
warranty is made regarding the positional or thematic accuracy of the 
GIS data. The GIS data and any features depicted do not represent or 
confer any legal rights, privileges, benefits, boundaries or claims of 
any kind. The Office of Planning and Sustainable Development encourages users to report any 
discrepancies or errors found. 
 Contact: Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, Office of Planning and 
Sustainable Development, State of Hawaii; PO Box 2359, Honolulu, Hi. 
96804; (808) 587-2846; email: gis@hawaii.gov. Website: https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis.</useconst>
        <datacred>Hawaii State Department of Health; Hawaii Statewide GIS Program</datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20201101</metd>
        <metc>
            <cntinfo>
                <!--no contact person or organization name available-->
            </cntinfo>
        </metc>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
