<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>Roads - Honolulu County</title>
                <onlink>https://geodata.hawaii.gov/arcgis/rest/services/Transportation/MapServer/3</onlink>
                <onlink>https://files.hawaii.gov/dbedt/op/gis/data/streets_oah.pdf</onlink>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>[Metadata]  Description:  Streets for the island of Oahu only as of May, 2021.Source:  Honolulu Land Information System (HOLIS), C&amp;amp;C of Honolulu, May 20, 2022.For additional information, please refer to complete metadata at https://files.hawaii.gov/dbedt/op/gis/data/streets_oah.pdf or contact Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, Office of Planning and Sustainable Development, State of Hawaii; PO Box 2359, Honolulu, HI 96804; (808) 587-2846; email: gis@hawaii.gov; Website: https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis.NOTE: This layer is maintained by the C&amp;amp;C of Honolulu HOLIS. It
 is provided on the State of Hawaii GIS ArcGIS Online and downloading sites as a service to
 the public. Data is downloaded from the C&amp;amp;C website periodically. To obtain the latest version of the Oahu Street Centerline layer, users should visit the HOLIS Open Geospatial Data Portal at https://honolulu-cchnl.opendata.arcgis.com/. </abstract>
            <purpose>Roads - Honolulu County, as of May, 2021.</purpose>
        </descript>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>Oahu</themekey>
                <themekey>Roads</themekey>
                <themekey>Hawaii</themekey>
                <themekey>Honolulu</themekey>
                <themekey>Streets</themekey>
                <themekey>Transportation</themekey>
                <themekey>Centerlines</themekey>
                <themekey>HawaiiStateGIS</themekey>
                <themekey>histategis</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>Other Constraints</accconst>
        <useconst>State of Hawaii Terms of Use. 



The
 contents of this web page are public domain and to the extent indicated
 otherwise in the Terms of Use, are exempt from Terms of Use policy 
restrictions.There are no expressed warranties associated with the 
release of this data or product. Specifically, no warranty is made that 
the GIS data or any subsequent updates will be error free and no 
warranty is made regarding the positional or thematic accuracy of the 
GIS data. The GIS data and any features depicted do not represent or 
confer any legal rights, privileges, benefits, boundaries or claims of 
any kind. The Office of Planning and Sustainable Development encourages users to report any 
discrepancies or errors found.  Contact: Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, Office of Planning and Sustainable Development, State of Hawaii; PO Box 2359, Honolulu, Hi. 96804; (808) 587-2846; email: gis@hawaii.gov. Website: https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis.</useconst>
        <datacred>Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, HOLIS</datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20190329</metd>
        <metc>
            <cntinfo>
                <!--no contact person or organization name available-->
            </cntinfo>
        </metc>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
